<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>poem on dave</title>
    <link>https://davebrothers.com/tags/poem/</link>
    <description>Recent content in poem on dave</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://davebrothers.com/tags/poem/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Message From Oakville</title>
      <link>https://davebrothers.com/blog/message-from-oakville/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davebrothers.com/blog/message-from-oakville/</guid>
      <description>We left this morning,around 3,when the pull of the moonwas so fiercethat little trickles of river watercame marching through the sliding door,and we prayed.As we followed Polaris out of town,we swept around thechair of Cassiopeia,mouthing herlip servicesand sweet-nothing niceties, lifting her our complimentarysacrifices,our whispered lambs.I wondered what __________ would do.Out Highway 99,the rivers were topping outover the surface of the road -–Our green Ethiopia is falling,we murmured over the low droneof the engine bearing us away,Can you still not stay Poseidon’s wrath?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memento</title>
      <link>https://davebrothers.com/blog/memento/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davebrothers.com/blog/memento/</guid>
      <description>Eve rose out of Adam,simian and unerect,covered in dust.She reached outand held his facein her thick-skinnedhands, still warmfrom the afterbirth,and breathed.I see numbnessin your eyes,she said,and spun awayin a pillar of flame.In the ring ofsmoldering earthshe left behind,Adam placed an apple,fat with the waterof unmade memory,and as he cried, clutching ground litterto his cold, wreckedframe, thesyrupy sapfrom the half-eaten fruitstretched and soakedinto the asheson the ground.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sketch for A.G.</title>
      <link>https://davebrothers.com/blog/sketch-for-ag/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davebrothers.com/blog/sketch-for-ag/</guid>
      <description>There was only the momentand the mourning –sheer black veilsand the silence that pricksmoving out of the stage lightand into blackmerging into blackmerging into black.
Silence is not enough,he said, narrating,and clappedlike the thunder that spokein the first wash ofwet noisein the first lightof an August morning –It is the thunder that endures,the primordial Donnerthat blinds more than the Blitz.There were mumblingsin the lobby that night,low utterances of wasteand the thin flick ofspent tickets in the handsof those who failed to speak.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>